Alderfer, S. Stanley Arbitration Files 5576
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration Decisions, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: NEAPCO Products, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2479, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    6/15/61. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside of Classification.
  - Item 2: Lipsett Steel Products, Incorporated, Coatesville, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5856, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    3/30/61. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 3: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    5/11/61. Issue: Reduction in Force.
  - Item 4: Radio Corporation of America vs. Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    1/31/61.Issue: Contract Interpretation (attendance at arbitration hearing).
  - Item 5: R.T. French Company vs. Warehouse Employees Union, Local 169, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    4/20/61. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 6: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    11/10/61. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 7: Steel Heddle Manufacturing Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5420, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    11/27/61. Issue: Working Conditions.
  - Item 8: Westmoreland Metal Manufacturing Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4506, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    12/18/61. Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Suspensions.
  - Item 9: Link-Belt Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    3/9/61. Issue: Funeral Leave and Funeral Pay.
  - Item 10: General Steel Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2323, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    7/7/61. Issue: Discharge.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Beloit Eastern Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5677, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    2/9/62. Issue: Discipline.
  - Item 2: Philco Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 102, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    1/62. Issue: Union Representatives and Business.
  - Item 3: York Division of The Bendix Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 114, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    4/5/62. Issue: Classification of Jobs; Past Practice; Seniority; Safety.
  - Item 4: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation, Industrial Equipment Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    10/20/62. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 5: Ellwood Ivins Steel Tube Works, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1619, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    12/7/62. Issue: Shutdown--Vacation Pay.
  - Item 6: Cramp Shipbuilding and Drydock Company vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 329, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    12/17/62. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 7: Purolator Products, Incorporated vs. District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 13659, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    1/2/62. Issue: Arbitrability; Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge No. 1717, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
    10/11/63. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 2: Globe Hoist Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3529, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
    4/25/63. Issue: Time Studies.
  - Item 3: Michael Flynn Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local 502, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
    12/31/63. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
  - Item 4: Crown Paper Board Company, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 286, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
    7/63. Issue: Layoff.
  - Item 5: Container Corporation of America vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 807, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
    11/12/63. Issue: Reinstatement; Back Pay Awards.
  - Item 6: Baldwin-Lime-Hamilton Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
    10/25/63. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 7: Fibre-Metal Products Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5739, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
    11/21/63. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 8: Atlas Chemical Industries, Incorporated vs. District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 13101, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 21)
    3/2/63. Issue: Seniority.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Philco Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Radio and Television Workers Local 101, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 22)
    11/64. Issue: Transfers--Bargaining Unit Work.
  - Item 2: Penco Products Incorporated, Oaks, Pennsylvania vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local 502, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 22)
    5/15/64. Issue: Elimination of Jobs.
  - Item 3: Phoenix Manufacturing Company, Division - Union Tank Car Company Catasauqua Plant vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Lodge 1506, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 22)
    5/1/64. Issue: Management Rights.
  - Item 4: Pennsylvania Forge, Division of Chemetron Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists, District Lodge 1, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 22)
    7/30/64. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
  - Item 5: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 22)
    6/3/64. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 6: The Philadelphia Inquirer vs. Philadelphia Newspaper and Magazine Chauffeurs and Handlers, Local 628, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 22)
    8/3/64. Issue: Discharge.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Fibre Metal Products Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5739, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 23)
    2/23/65. Issue: Overtime.
  - Item 2: American Sugar Company, Franklin Refinery vs. Sugar Refinery Workers' Union, Local 1650, Sugar Workers Council of North America, I.L.A., 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 23)
    7/3/65. Issue: Evaluation of Job Factors.
  - Item 3: Crown Paperboard Company vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 286, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 23)
    11/29/65. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 4: National Gypsum Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5476, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 23)
    2/3/65. Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
  - Item 5: I.T.T. Nesbitt Company, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1385, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 23)
    6/21/65. Issue: Discipline.
  - Item 6: Penco Products, Incorporated, Oaks, Pennsylvania vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local 502, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 23)
    4/24/65. Issue: Seniority.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Triangle Publications, Incorporated, Radio and Television Division (WFIL, WFIL-FM, and WFIL-TV) vs. International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, Television Broadcasting Studio Employees, Local 804, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 24)
    2/25/66. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 2: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 195, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 24)
    7/22/66. Issue: Overtime.
  - Item 3: Triangle, Incorporated, Gravure Division vs. International Photo Engravers Union of North America (IPEU of NA), Local 7, Philadelphia Photo-Engravers' Union, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 24)
    4/14/66. Issue: Transfers.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: International Telephone and Telegraph, ITT Nesbitt Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1385, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 25)
    2/67. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 2: Penco Products, Incorporated, Oaks, Pennsylvania vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local 502, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 25)
    7/29/67. Issue: Suspension.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Cutler-Hammer, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1972, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
    8/9/68. Issue: Vacation Pay.
  - Item 2: Badenhausen Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5586, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
    2/68. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Bargaining Unit Work.
  - Item 3: AMATEK Incorporated, U.S. Gauge Division vs. International Association of Machinists, Bux-Mont Lodge 1092, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
    1/5/68. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 4: American Safety Equipment Company, Darby, Pennsylvania vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
    4/3/68. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 5: Chemical Leaman Tank Lines, Incorporated vs. Tank Truck Workers Union, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
    7/24/68. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 6: Fischer and Porter Company vs. Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
    12/10/68. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 7: Kawecki Chemical Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 619, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
    11/18/68. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 8: Thriftway Foods, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 384, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 26)
    12/23/68. Issue: Suspension.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1967-1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    5/16/69. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 2: Interstate Iron and Supply Company vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local 502, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    3/21/69. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 3: Nicholson File Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4825, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    3/69. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 4: The Steel Heddle Manufacturing Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5420, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    6/69. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 5: The Beryllium Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    2/28/69. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 6: DeLaval Turbine, Incorporated, Trenton, New Jersey vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    7/18/69. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 7: Allied Printing Employers' Association and Cuneo Eastern Press, Incorporated of Pennsylvania vs. Philadelphia Printing Pressmen's Union No. 4 and Philadelphia Press Assistants' Union No. 11, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    6/30/69. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
  - Item 8: Zoological Society of Philadelphia vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 752, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    10/28/69. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 9: Glenco Refrigeration Corporation, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 123, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    8/69. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 10: Superior Tube Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6816, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    1/2/70. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 11: The Steel Heddle Manufacturing Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5420, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    10/31/67. Issue: Arbitrability.
  - Item 12: Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    11/69. Issue: Demotion; Assignment to Work Outside Classification; Working Conditions.
  - Item 13: Elwood Ivins Steel Tube Works, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6342, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    12/18/69. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 14: Specialty Precision Wire Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7254, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    12/69. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 15: Hoffman Industries, Incorporated, Sinking Spring, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5655, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 27)
    7/69. Issue: Union Security.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1963-1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Linc-Belt Company, Philadelphia Operation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828., 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 28)
    2/2/67. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 2: Linc-Belt Company, Philadelphia Operation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828., 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 28)
    8/1/63. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
  - Item 3: Linc-Belt Company, Philadelphia Operation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828., 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 28)
    7/24/65. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 4: Linc-Belt Company, Philadelphia Operation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828., 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 28)
    2/2/67. Issue: Demotions.
  - Item 5: Linc-Belt Division, FMC Corporation, Philadelphia Operations vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 28)
    9/20/69. Issue: Safety.
  - Item 6: Linc-Belt Division, FMC Corporation, Philadelphia Operations vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 28)
    9/20/69. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 7: Linc-Belt Company, Philadelphia Operation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828., 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 28)
    7/24/65. Issue: Layoff.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Riley Stoker Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2954, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    7/27/70. Issue: Contracting Out.
  - Item 2: International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation, ITT Nesbitt Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1385, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    10/30/70. Issue: Schedules of Work.
  - Item 3: SKF Industries vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    4/7/70. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 4: Armour Industrial Chemical Company vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-398, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    4/70. Issue: Schedules of Work; Suspension; Discharge.
  - Item 5: Fayette R. Plumb, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7411, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    5/4/70. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 6: Arcos Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4538, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    5/27/70. Issue: Schedules of Work; Discharge.
  - Item 7: Precision Drawn Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6177, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    7/70. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 8: Riley Stoker Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2960, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    10/27/70. Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
  - Item 9: Riley Stoker Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2954, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    7/31/70. Issue: Alcoholism, Drinking and Intoxication; Holidays and Holiday Pay.
  - Item 10: Sorensen Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5424, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    7/31/70. Issue: Seniority--Layoff.
  - Item 11: Armour Industrial Chemical Company vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-398, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    8/70. Issue: Overtime.
  - Item 12: John Wood Company, Conshohocken Plant vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2964, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    12/15/70. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 13: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 29)
    10/30/70. Issue: Reinstatement.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Krylon Department, Chemical Division, Borden, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5740, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    9/28/71. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 2: Delroyd Division, DeLaval Turbine Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6061, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    4/30/71. Issue: Safety.
  - Item 3: Bethlehem Fabricators, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1371, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    5/10/71. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 4: Food Fair Stores, Incorporated vs. Retail Clerks Union, Local 1357, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    6/17/71. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 5: J. Chein and Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4725, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    5/25/71. Issue: Seniority; Carelessness.
  - Item 6: Honorbilt Products, Incorporated, Serta Mattress Company Division vs. Upholsterers' International Union of North America, United Bedding and Glider Workers Local 404, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    8/12/71. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 7: Mainland Regional High School District of Atlantic County, Board of Education vs. Mainland Teachers' Association, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    10/12/71. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 8: Valley Engineering and Manufacturing Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 125, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    10/13/71. Issue: Discharge; Vacation Pay.
  - Item 9: Link-Belt Enclosed Drive Division, FMC Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7805, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    10/20/71. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 10: Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Transportation Checkers, Receivers and Clerical Workers, Local 161, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 30)
    7/12/71. Issue: Reinstatement.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Certain-Teed/Saint Gobain Insulation Corporation, Berlin, New Jersey vs. Glass Bottle Blowers Association, Local 103, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    8/1/72. Issue: Discipline.
  - Item 2: Heintz Division, Kelsey-Hayes Company, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Equipment Workers of America, Local 834, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    8/9/72. Issue: Sick Leave and Sick Pay.
  - Item 3: Palmer-Shile Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4193, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    7/28/72. Issue: Suspension; Discharge.
  - Item 4: New Jersey Water Company vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 473, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    7/26/72. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 5: American Chain and Cable Company, Incorporated, York Chain Plant vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1852, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    5/22/72. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
  - Item 6: Ellwood Ivins Tube Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6342, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    5/22/72. Issue: Assignment of Jobs; Vacations.
  - Item 7: Chamberlain Manufacturing Corporation, Burlington, New Jersey vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7108, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    3/6/72. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 8: Krylon Department, Chemical Division, Borden, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5740, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    4/24/72. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 9: Food Fair Stores, Incorporated vs. Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 169, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    5/12/72. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 10: RCA Corporation vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 241, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    7/20/72. Issue: Layoff.
  - Item 11: Container Corporation of America, Baltimore Container Plant vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union No. 481, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    5/8/72. Issue: Rates of Pay; Discharge.
  - Item 12: Container Corporation of America vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 392, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 13: New Jersey Bell Telephone vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey, Local 827, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    6/1/72. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 14: RCA Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 103, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    2/24/72. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 15: General Battery Corporation, Hamburg, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4425, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    3/11/72. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 16: Vertol Division, The Boeing Company vs. International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1069, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    10/26/72. Issue: Arbitrability.
  - Item 17: Hofmann Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5655, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    2/3/72. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 18: RCA Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 103, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    11/8/72. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 19: National Sugar Refining Company vs. Sugar Refinery Workers Union, Local 1648, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    11/13/72. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 20: Armak Chemicals Division, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-398, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    9/6/72. Issue: Testing of Employees.
  - Item 21: DeLaval Turbine Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    10/4/72. Issue: Merit Increases and Merit Review.
  - Item 22: Calbar, Incorporated and Kenmar Manufacturing Company, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 169, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    11/10/72. Issue: Discharge.